Our tools are pretty few.
We--to be a sportswriter you're going to need a tape recorder, a notebook, a good supply of pens, a good supply of batteries to keep your tape recorder running, and then a laptop.
That's really it.
Most of us don't keep regular office hours.
In my case I work more from home, and I work more from the college here that I cover, than I do actually at the office.
So I don't carry a lot of stuff other than a satchel over my shoulder with a laptop and pens and notebooks and tape recorders, and that's basically the tools of the trade.
You're gathering information and you're sending it into your newspaper through your laptop, which you're probably going to need wireless capability on your laptop would be a big help.
Many of the press boxes that we work in have wireless signals, and that helps you transmit your story back to your newspaper.
But, we don't have a lot.
It could be kept in one backpack or one satchel, and that's about it.
Probably fax machines.
I can even remember telecopiers, and these were ways that--this is before e-mail even came along, I had been doing some of this work.
And there was no opportunity to send in a story or send information back and forth through e-mail.
So, it was through fax machines or telecopiers, and we've gotten completely rid of those kinds of things in terms of sharing information back and forth, or me getting an article into my newspaper.
It's all done through e-mail now.
So, it's just much more streamlined now.
It's faster, and we have definitely ridden the wave of technology in this business like everybody else has.